grandmafriends.com 2014-06-22

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy**

**Our Commitment To Privacy Your privacy is important to us**.  
To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.   
The Information We Collect: "Name" and "Email address" 

**The Way We Use Information:**   
Send out verification of orders placed and retrieve lost passwords.

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**   
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by using your account information a Billing website. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.   
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us:**  
Please send us all questions to email [cs@nwm-support.com](mailto:cs@nwm-support.com)
